So, the short list of 30 was announced
for the Ballon d'Or today. Harry Kane is
your odds-on favorite according to the
bookies, followed by Lionel Messi. Rodri
is there to win it once again. Kylian
Mbappé, Khvicha Kvaratskhelia, given his
performance for PSG. Lionel Messi and
Fabián Ruiz, very much an outsider, but
if you're voting on trophies, he's won
more than anyone, and that is why Don is
going for Fabián Ruiz first, Jamal Kane,
Mbappé, and Alisson.
>> Say his top five.
>> Don, he's not he's not
Don
Don he's been on the he's on the loopy
juice.
>> Uh Ian Darke tweeted as much as Harry
Kane would deserve to win the Ballon
d'Or. Kylian Mbappé's case is pretty
strong, too, having won the Golden Boot
and become the highest scorer in World
Cup history. I know this is completely
the wrong panel for this discussion.
>> right? The
>> I know I don't want to Yes.
>> A Ballon d'Or winner, who Listen, let me
just put it one way. Fabián Ruiz is a
very good player.
>> Yes.
>> But Fabián Ruiz was not a regular for
Spain at the World Cup. I don't believe
that they chopped and changed, right?
Again, we're not talking
You're right. This is the wrong panel.
>> Yes.
>> This is just the wrong panel. Full stop.
Even bring this up.
>> No, that's all right,
guys.
>> It's the wrong panel. However, what I'm
going to say is it's not it can't it
cannot just be about trophies.
>> Right.
>> It cannot. And I know people say, "Well,
yeah." It cannot just be about that
because that's team.
That's a team.
>> So, would you have Kane?
>> I would because that's an incredible
>> 61.
Incredible consistency, incredible
consistency all the way through.
>> [laughter]
>> And I don't I don't care what he's won
or what he didn't win.
That That's
>> What about those that would say, "Yes,
but if Kylian Mbappé was playing in
Germany and playing for Bayern Munich,
then he would have eclipsed Harry
>> what I would say to that Well, Kylian
Mbappé is not playing in Germany. So,
get you know,
So, we don't know. That's It's
hypothetical for those hypothetical
morons out there. I don't know that I
don't have the answer to that. Harry
Kane's all round game, right, as well as
the goals, is something to behold.
The way that he drops, the way that he
passes it, the way that he finishes, the
So, I would I think that would be a
If he loves the Ballon d'Or, and he may
or may not, be a good recognition
uh of
the way he's conducted himself for club
and country through his career,
finishing off with a uh spectacular
season at Bayern last year, rather than
the usual suspects. And I don't know
where Don has pulled that from. I know
where he's from.
>> Uh Frank?
>> Yeah, I don't I mean, to answer to Don,
you know, remember in 2022, I put Julian
Alvarez because he won four
four trophies. He was the one in the
world who won who won the most trophies.
And of course, Messi got the the Ballon
d'Or. Uh so, I'm pretty sure Fabinho is
won't get it. But it's crazy because why
don't you put a Kubasi as well as a
favorite because he he won everything as
well. He had a great season. He had a
great World Cup. He's a great kid. But
of course, he's a defender, so he's not
going to get it. This why we are we are
the wrong panel because it doesn't mean
anything, and we all know that. And it's
always the same people who's going to
get it. So, I would be happy to have
Harry Kane winning because that guy is
more for his career, I would say,
overall than his his perfor- his
performances last season.
Uh but I I I don't even know what to
say. I'm fed up with that. Really, it's
boring. It's It doesn't mean anything.
It's It's settled on nothing. So, carry
on enjoying it, but leave me alone with
that.
>> Yeah. Robert
>> At least I tried.
>> No, yeah, no, you did try. No, I I
appreciate it.
>> I I wouldn't have anything against Kane
winning it. I wouldn't have anything
against Mbappé winning it. But I'm going
to go on who I would like to see most
watch who I like to watch most, who
excites me most. It's Jamal. Whenever he
gets the ball, whenever he's playing, I
just love to see him.
>> wait a minute.
>> [laughter]
>> That's a great way to his press
conference. It's interesting you say
that, Robert, because Lamine Yamal
talked about the Ballon d'Or yesterday.
>> Oh my god.
>> Slightly different to what we've seen
from Ballon d'Or candidates in the past,
Frank. He's not going to run a campaign.
He's not going to tell you what he
wants. It's up to you.
>> Yeah, and and so
You know what? I kept I don't I don't
follow La Liga. It's not my duty.
And and I but I kept on on hearing I
kept on hearing last year that the
Lamine Yamal was on the same level that
he was two years ago, that he was
injured, that he didn't he needed some
time to recover. So, why do you want to
put on the Ballon d'Or? If he had six
months
>> think you cared. I didn't think you
cared.
>> Oh, I don't care.
>> So, then why why are you why are you
telling me that Lamine Yamal doesn't
deserve it if you don't care?
>> WELL, WELL, YOU KNOW, according to the
to the situation, normally you have to
have a great season
scoring many goals because it's only
about scoring goals and and number 10 or
strikers. The others we don't care. So
that wasn't the case with Lamine Yamal.
It's what I heard from everybody saying
that last season. So why would he be one
of the favorite if he if he didn't have
the season that he had the season before
and he didn't get the season before. I'm
just saying that. So but I wish him good
luck because he's very young, very
talented. I love him and I wish him to
win whatever he wants.
>> What's the Spanish word for Muppet?
>> [laughter]
>> El El Muppetso?
>> You'll not know this because he's
basically saying what Lamine Yamal is
basically saying is all you Muppets out
there don't really I've won the I've won
the Liga. I've won the European
Championships. I just won the World Cup,
you know, Ballon d'Or. He's basically
saying I mean I'm sure he wouldn't turn
it down but he's basically saying look,
I've got bigger fish to fry.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, we we want to retain we want
to win La Liga for the third year in a
row.
Uh we want to win the Champions League
which they haven't done under Hansi
Flick. Uh we want to win the big things.
And I'll let everybody else, you he's
saying get this guy and I'm going to
high five him.
You the media uh
>> I'm sure that'll be the highlight of his
year as well.
>> Get down AFC. Now Lamine you the media
can talk about it all you want. I've got
bigger things to worry about. That's a
very mature answer.
>> Yeah, it was a mature answer, wasn't it
Robert?
>> Yeah.
It was a mature answer, you know. And
I'm not sure where Frank gets his
information from. He was only about the
last six games he missed and up to that
point he was absolutely magnificent. It
was Raphinha who had a difficult season
because he was injured a lot more.
Lamine Yamal was absolutely magnificent.
Didn't play his best at the World Cup
but what a player.
>> There you are, passive aggressive
Robert. Good way to end that segment.
Third
>> I'm going to go at Rob Palmer. He's
going to go at Frank Leboeuf.
>> Uh no Christian Cristiano Ronaldo on the
list. Even the media could drop him
unlike Roberto Martinez. Uh no Pedri
either. Pedri of course uh missing a lot
of the campaign as well because of
injury.
Uh
Fútbol Fútbol Americas will definitely
be sure be talking about Ballon d'Or on
the next edition 8:30 Eastern on
Thursday.